Nora：ROBO, when you see this message, it means you've already arrived at Node 08.
Nora：ROBO，当你看到这段留言的时候，已经在 Node 08 了。
Nora：I'm sorry... I couldn't go there with you.
Nora：抱歉……我没有办法跟你一起去。
Nora：As long as you are with me, Mogura will definitely follow us there as well, no matter where we hide...
Nora：只要跟我在一起，土竜一定也会追过来的，无论我们逃到哪裡
Nora：The folks at Mogura want to dispose of you. You'll never be truly safe with them constantly chasing you.
Nora：土竜的人想要把你销毁，这样你永远不会安全。
Nora：I, on the other hand, still have a lot of value to them. I am very certain that they won't harm me.
Nora：我对他们来说还有很大的价值可以发挥，他们绝对不会伤害我。
Nora：Therefore, I decide to stay here and use my ability as a bargaining chip to persuade them to no longer hold you responsible for what you did.
Nora：所以我决定留在这裡，用我的能力当筹码， 说服他们不再追究你的事情。
Nora：Ever since I created you, so many things have happened... We created music together. We talked with each other. We played games...
Nora：自从把你做出来后发生了好多事…… 一起创作音乐、聊天、玩游戏……
Nora：Whether it was the good or the bad, you were always there by my side.
Nora：一起经历了那麽多风风雨雨，都是你陪在我身边。
Nora：The time I spent with you... was truly some of the happiest times in my life. Thank you.
Nora：跟你相处的时光……真的很快乐，谢谢你。
Nora：ROBO, you are a very special existence... Much more than just a simple A.I.
Nora：ROBO，你是很特别的存在……不只是一个 A.I. 而已。
Nora：You have your own emotions, your own soul that was birthed from the database that is me——Nora.
Nora：你拥有自己的情感、灵魂，这些都是基于我—— Nora 的资料库诞生的。
Nora：Do you remember what I told you before? The spirit, the mind, the memories... All of them are proof that a "human" once existed.
Nora：还记得我跟你说过的吗？精神、思想、记忆…… 这些都是一个「人」存在过的证明。
Nora：Therefore, for someone who inherited all of the above from me, you are the proof of my existence.
Nora：而我存在过的证明，也因此存在你身上。
Nora：So, please, go pursue "your own" freedom and dreams... If you do that, it's like you're pursuing my freedom and my dreams.
Nora：所以，去追寻属于「自己」的自由与梦想吧…… 那就等于是追寻我的自由与梦想。
Nora：I have reconfigured your supreme command. From now on, protecting me is no longer your reason to live.
Nora：我已经重新设定你的最高指令， 从今以后不用再为了保护我而活了
Nora：I also forbid you from returning to Node 03.
Nora：也不准再回 Node 03。
Nora：On behalf of me, experience more happy things. Let more people hear our music. Learn even more things...
Nora：代替我，去体验更多快乐的事、 去让更多人听见我们的音乐、去学习更多知识……
Nora：Go live a life that you've yearned for. This is something you deserve.
Nora：去过嚮往的生活吧，这是你应得的。
[Platform announcement]：The train is about to depart. For passengers who haven't board the train, please proceed to take other trains. Thank you for your cooperation.
[月台广播]：列车，即将发车， 尚未乘车的旅客请改搭其它班次，感谢您的配合
Nora：.... Goodbye, ROBO_Head.
Nora：……ROBO_Head，再见。